fit.edu 2019-07-07

# Web Privacy Policy

##### Effective Date May 25, 2018

 **Internet Privacy Policy**

As one of the world's leading technological universities, we are especially aware of both Internet and personal data privacy issues domestically and internationally. Your privacy is very important to us. The following information explains the Internet privacy policy and practices the University has adopted for its website.

You never have to share personal information with us to visit our website. No personal information about you is collected unless you affirmatively choose to make such information available to us.

Florida Tech collects only the most general information from you while you visit our website. By the time you leave, we'll know your native country, the browser you use, the site that directed you to us and your Internet address. This information is compiled into a summary of all site users and is not linked to personal information. We use this information only in the interest of better understanding our visitors so we can make this website better. To expedite the process the website uses “cookies” which enable the website to tailor what you see based upon how you entered the site and make it more convenient to use.

If you choose to share personal information with us, by sending us a message or filling out a form, we will use the information only for the purposes authorized.  So for example, if you provide us with information through an online admission application, that data will only be used for that purpose. We will not disclose the information to third parties or government agencies, unless required to do so by law. If we are required to disclose information about you by law, we will endeavor to notify you of the disclosure in advance.

Florida Tech will retain personal information no longer than necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was provided and to satisfy its legal requirements; including insuring that our data processing is in compliance with and will satisfy our legal and regulatory obligations (e.g., audit, accounting, academic records, and statutory retention terms), dispute resolution, and the establishment, assertion or defense of legal claims.

International regulations entitle residents of the European Union (EU)  to the following rights with regards to their personal data: right to be informed, right to erasure, right to data portability, right to access, right to rectification, right to restrict processing, right to object, and rights related to automated decision making that conform with the General Data Protection Regulations for the EU, which can found online at; <https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection_en>,   These rights are recognized by Florida Tech and are administered  through Florida Tech’s Data Privacy Officer, [privacy@fit.edu](mailto:privacy@fit.edu)

Our website may contain links to third party websites that we do not control or maintain. The owners of these websites may have information practices that differ from ours. Visitors should consult privacy notices of third party websites before submitting any personally identifiable information. We have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, third parties.

If you have questions about our privacy policy, GPDR, or the use and removal of cookies, please contact Florida Tech’s Data Privacy Officer, at [privacy@fit.edu](mailto:privacy@fit.edu) or call the 321-674-8100.

If you have more general questions about the Florida Tech website, feel free to use our convenient online form at <http://webservices.fit.edu/requests/> , email us at [www@fit.edu](mailto:www@fit.edu) or call us at 321-674-7255
